We Can't Stop
我们不能停止
歌手：Miley Cyrus
压制:随Feng
It's our party we can do what we want
这是我们的派对 我们可以做任何想做的
It's our party we can say what we want
这是我们的派对 我们可以说任何想说的
It's our party we can love who we want
这是我们的聚会 我们可以去爱任何想爱的人
We can kiss who we want
我们可以亲吻任何人
Red cups and sweaty bodies everywhere
红色的杯子和出汗的身体无处不在
Hands in the air like we don't care
双手在空气中就像我们不在乎
Cause we came to have so much fun now
因为现在我们来到这儿得到了更多乐趣
Got somebody here might get some now
也许现在某些人会得到一些
If you're not ready to go home
如果你没准备好回家
Can I get a hell no
我是否可以带你们一起彻底疯狂
Cause we gonna go all night
因为我们要疯狂整个晚上
Till we see the sunlight alright
知道我们能够看到早上的阳光
So la da da di we like to party
所以我们喜欢聚会
Dancing with Miley
与MILEY 跳舞
Doing whatever we want
做我们喜欢做的事
This is our house
这是我们的房子
This is our rules
这是我们的规则
And we can't stop
我们无法停下
And we won't stop
并且我们不愿停下
Can't you see it's we who own the night
难道你看不到我们拥有整个夜晚吗
Can't you see it we who bout' that life
难道你看不到我们与那命运较量
And we can't stop
然而我们无法停止
And we won't stop
并且我们也不想停止
We run things, things don't run we
我们去为了一些事努力 但却事与愿违
Don't take nothing from nobody
不要在意别人的意见
It's our party we can do what we want
这是我们的聚会 我们可以做任何想做的
It's our party we can say what we want
这是我们的聚会 我们可以说任何想说的
It's our party we can love who we want
这是我们的聚会 我们可以去爱任何想爱的人
We can kiss who we want
我们可以亲吻我们想亲吻的人
To my homegirls here with the big butts
家乡的女孩身材火辣
Shaking it like we at a strip club
摇晃着她的臀部就像在脱衣舞会一样
Remember only God can judge us
记住只有上帝能裁决我们
Forget the haters cause somebody loves ya
让我们忘记恨 因为我们有很多人的爱
And everyone in line in the bathroom
所有聚会的人都在浴室排队
Trying to get a line in the bathroom
试图在浴室排队
We all so turnt up here
我们欢呼雀跃
Getting turnt up yea yea
让我们欢呼雀跃
So la da da di we like to party
所以我们喜欢派对
Dancing with Miley
和麦莉一起跳舞
Doing whatever we want
做我们想要做的
This is our house
这是我们的房子
This is our rules
这是我们的规矩
And we can't stop
我们不能停止
And we won't stop
我们不会停止
Can't you see it's we who own the night
你没看到这就是我们的夜晚吗
Can't you see it we who bout' that life
你没看到这就是我们的生活吗
And we can't stop
我们不能停止
And we won't stop
我们不会停止
We run things, things don't run we
我们去为了一些事努力 但却事与愿违
Don't take nothing from nobody
不要在意别人的意见
It's our party we can do what we want
这是我们的聚会 我们可以做任何想做的
It's our party we can say what we want
这是我们的聚会 我们可以说任何想说的
It's our party we can love who we want
这是我们的聚会 我们可以去爱任何想爱的人
We can kiss who we want
我们可以亲吻任何人
We can live how we want
我们可以过想要的生活
It's our party we can do what we want to
这是我们的聚会 我们可以做任何想做的
It's our house we can love who we want to
这是我们的房子 我们可以去爱任何想爱的人
It's our song we can sing if we want to
这是我们的歌 我们想唱就唱
It's my mouth I can say what I want to
嘴是我的 我想说就说
Yea, Yea, Yeah, Yeah
Yea Yea Yeah Yeah
And we can't stop
我们不能停止
And we won't stop
我们不会停止
We run things, things don't run we
我们去为了一些事努力 但却事与愿违
Don't take nothing from nobody
不要在意别人的意见
Yea, Yea, Yeah, Yeah
Yea Yea Yeah Yeah